<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Love</string>
    <string name="intro_txt">I will Start with a Quote. "TO THE WORLD,YOU MAY BE THE ONE PERSON, BUT TO THE ONE PERSON YOU MAY BE THE WORLD…" And Trust me For Me, You are the World.
    It all started in the School Bus. First I heard your voice and then I looked back to see who has such melodious voice, and I saw you. It all Started then and there.
    I came home, and I had got only one question in mind That What is her name? After a Lot of research I managed to know Your name i.e. Buchi.
    "MAINE TO BAS TUMHE YU HI MUD KAR DEKHA THA, KYA PTA THA KI MUJHE TUMHARI AADAT HI HO JAEGI. AUR ISS AADAT KO MAI PYAAR V KARNE LAGUNGA".
    To describe How Beautiful you are for me, I have No Words just a ton of feelings, All I will say is "YOU ARE THE GIRL FOR WHICH THE MOON CHASED AND STARS WISHED FOR".
    </string>

    <string name="cute">
        Harshita:  There is no words to express how I feel about you...U r my everything,my world,my life,my soul..U r what l really need in my life U r my first thought in the morning  Nd last thought before l fall asleep... I truly could not live my life without uhh.l  know l may vry careless at times but l Love uhh from d bottom of my heart.U have change my life in a better that u r now an indispensible part of it without whom l can\'t even imagine my life going on...U not only make me smile but also listen my silly joke Nd Rythemless songs.. U R MY END ND MY BEGINNING,, EVEN WHEN I LOSE I AM WINNING..COZ ALL OF ME ..LOVES ALL OF YOU - I know these are the stolen lines but yes it holds true in our story.Every morning u gave me a reason to start a day..Thnk uhh for coming in my life. (सच में मैं तुमसे बहुत-बहुत बहुत-बहुत बहुत प्यार करती हूं।)l Love uhh a lot se bhi jda..
        \nAlok: There are a lot to say in reply of these sweet words but right now I am just Speechless after reading these lines. But Trust me, One thing is Sure at the End I will always Love You.
    </string>
    <string name="cute1">
        Hi Baby, Wish You a very Happy New Year 2018. I don\'t know what I want to say. You Know, I wonder every time what are the possible way to show How much I Love You, How much I care about you.Sometime I get successful and sometimes I fails. But just know One thing, All I do is Love, a Lot of Love. You know, finally I started realizing You are the one who understands and make us survive through bad times. Yaar Agar tm naa hote to mera kyaa hota. Harshita, I Love You so so so Much. Hamesha... We got many up and down since today but the best thing is Still we are together and Very Happy and even more closer. I am sorry for all my misbehave.Forgive me and I promise we will always be Together. I Love You Hamesha...
    </string>
</resources>
